Jeff Brozena, Teacher, Operator, Analyst

jeff@brozena.net | +1 (570)335-8269

CI	JN	ΔN	Æ.	۸ ۱	D٦	ί
0	\cup IN	/11N	/1/	ъ.	N	1

An operator-teacher with broad and deep experience at one of the country's largest and most respected privately-held Medicaid pediatric dental groups. I was entrusted to set strategic direction, improve core business processes and lead complex change shortly before a cross-generational ownership transfer was expected. My impact at this group was described "like a crater" by its ownership.

EXPERIENCE

The Smilist Management - Manager of Optimization

Feb 2018 — Aug 2018

Smiles 4 Keeps Pediatric Dentistry - Practice Operations

Aug 2012 - Nov 2017

- Responsible for a complete digital transformation in the midst of a generational ownership transfer, resulting in accurate third-party valuation of business.
- Spoke publicly at American Academy of Pediatric Dentistry, Pennsylvania Academy of Pediatric Dentistry on the subjects of digitization and compliant record-keeping.

Bedrock Technology - Technician Jan 2012 — Aug 2012

Appek Mobile Apps - Project Manager May 2011 — Dec 2012

Penn State University - HCI Lab - Research Assistant May 2009 — Jan 2010

Penn State University - Software Trainer Aug 2007 — Dec 2009

• Promoted to supervisory position in June, 2009.

AWARDS Rock Ethics Stand Up Award, Penn State University

Apr 2011

Emerging Scholars Fellowship, Active Minds, Inc.

Jan 2011

EDUCATION

Pennsylvania State University

Aug 2008 — Aug 2019

BS - Information Sciences & Technology

SKILLS

Leadership: Public speaking, Systems thinking, Whole systems management, Written & verbal clarity, Motivational interviewing, Situational leadership

Digital transformation: Software training, Transformational change, Change management, Strategic planning, Business analysis

Healthcare information technology (HIT): HIPAA compliance, Electronic data interchange (EDI), Electronic medical record (EMR), Analytics, SQL, Product management, Systems integration, Software integration, Electronic remittance advice (ERA), Clinical decision support

Program management: Process improvement, Project management, Process optimization, Process management, Lean Six Sigma, Kaizen

REFERENCES

Dr Ross Wezmar, DDS: Jeff worked in an organization experiencing both cross-generational and analog-to-digital transformations. He maintained the delicate balance of transitioning a 40-year-old male-dominated enterprise to a second-generation female-directed organization in the fast-evolving provider side of healthcare. Throughout the transformation he kept steady focus on the ultimate goal of a successful transition. He shepherded cross-generational familial change in a focused and intelligent manner, holding true to both the original entrepreneurial drive along with the aspirations of the second generation. The business grew and all parties came to see the need for change while retaining the drive of the original owner. Much of this success is due to Jeff continually bringing clarity and tenacity of purpose to his position as a change-maker.

Dr Katherine Wezmar Poepperling, DDS: Jeff used his tremendous intellect combined with his insight into the human spirit to propel us in such a positive direction. He has given me a gift a peace which I didn't really think was possible.